question_data = [

    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "History",
        "question": "Former United States Presidents John Adams and Thomas Jefferson died within hours of each other.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "The average woman is 5 inches / 13 centimeters shorter than the average man.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "In the game Dead by Daylight, the killer Michael Myers is refered to as &quot;The Shape&quot;.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "In the video game &quot;Transistor&quot;, &quot;Red&quot; is the name of the main character.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "Pac-Man was invented by the designer Toru Iwatani while he was eating pizza.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Science: Computers",
        "question": "Early RAM was directly seated onto the motherboard and could not be easily removed.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "Luigi is taller than Mario?",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "History",
        "question": "In World War ll, Great Britian used inflatable tanks on the ports of Great Britain to divert Hitler away from Normandy/D-day landing.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
        "question": "The Angry Video Game Nerd&#039;s alter ego is &quot;Board James&quot;.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Geography",
        "question": "Italy and Ireland are the only countries in Europe that start with the letter I.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    }

]
